(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all visitors
本日ば！
Today!
角巻わため 2nd Live 「わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER」にご来場いただきまして、まことにありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to Tsunomaki Watame 2nd Live "Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER"!
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意ならびにご案内申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the show, I would like to give you some precautions and information.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は固くお断り致します。
The use of photography, audio recording, or video recording equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
会場内でのモッシュ・ダイブ・肩車、
Mosh pits, stage diving, or sitting on someone's shoulders in the venue,
ステージ上に物を投げ込む、
throwing objects onto the stage,
ステージ上に上がる、
going up on the stage,
故意に通路を塞ぐ、
intentionally blocking the aisles,
前に押し寄せる、
pushing toward the front,
周りのお客様のご迷惑となるような不自然なコール・奇声、
making unnatural calls or shouts that would disturb other guests,
公演の妨げとなるような大きな音を鳴らす等の行為、
acts such as making loud noises that would interfere with the performance,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、
violently waving both hands left and right at unnatural timing,
腕を振り回す・上半身をそらす…等の過激な応援行為、
extreme cheering acts such as swinging your arms around or leaning your upper body back,
過度なジャンプ行為…等
excessive jumping... and so on.
他のお客様のご迷惑になる、または公演を妨げる危険行為は一切禁止です。
Any dangerous acts that would cause trouble to other guests or interfere with the performance are strictly prohibited.
本公演は、映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席のお客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Cameras for video broadcasting and photography are inside the venue, and there may be instances where the audience in the seats is captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、予めご了承下さい。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes, etc.
万が一体調に異変を感じる場合は、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a staff member.
それでは！まもなく開演いたします！
Well then! The performance will begin shortly!
お席に着いてお待ち下さい！
Please wait at your seat!
以上、角巻わためでした！
That was Tsunomaki Watame!
推しの曲、めっちゃいいー。
The song of my fave is so good.
みるハコ チャンス！
Miru Haco Chance!
みるハコなら、臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miru Haco, you can enjoy your favorite content with a great sense of presence!
みるハコ最高！
Miru Haco is the best!
もっと盛り上がろう！
Let's get even more excited!
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miruhaco by JOYSOUND
こんばんドドド
Kon-ban-dododo
角巻ニュースのお時間です
It's time for Tsunomaki News.
角巻ニュースのお時間です。
いよいよ始まる!!
It's finally starting!!
角巻わため 2nd Live
Tsunomaki Watame's 2nd Live,
「わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER」で
"Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER."
販売しているグッズ紹介をしたいと思います!
I'd like to introduce the merchandise being sold!
まずは〜 こちら!!
First of all... this!!
「わためいとらいと」!!
"Watamate Light"!!
わためいとの形になっているペンライト!
A penlight shaped like a Watamate!
みんなで左右に振ったり
Everyone waving it side-to-side,
同じ色で揃えてみたり
matching colors,
会場のみんなも配信で見ているみんなも
everyone at the venue and everyone watching the stream,
一体になれる素敵なアイテムです!
it's a wonderful item that brings everyone together!
次に紹介するのは〜 こちら!!
The next one to introduce is... this!!
「アクリルペンライトスタンド」
"Acrylic Penlight Stand"
and「タペストリー」!!
and "Tapestry"!!
こちらがなんとペンライトと一緒に
These can actually be displayed
飾ることが出来るアクリルスタンドになっています!
together with the penlight!
タペストリーや他のライブグッズと一緒に並べて飾ってくださ〜い!
Please display them alongside the tapestry and other live merchandise!
まだまだあるよ〜! 次はこちら〜!!
There's still more! Next is this!!
「マフラータオル」!!
"Muffler Towel"!!
ライブで流した汗を拭いたり
Wiping sweat from the live,
掲げたり
holding it up,
いろんな使い方ができる定番アイテムです!
it's a classic item with various uses!
周りに気をつけながらタオルを振り回してもOKですよ〜!!
It's also okay to swing it around, just be careful of those around you!!
どんどん行きましょう! 次はこちら!
Let's keep going! Next is this!
「わためのおもしろなりきりサングラス」!
"Watame's Funny Cosplay Sunglasses"!
これをかけたらみんなもわためになれちゃうかも?
If you wear these, you might even become Watame yourself?
みんなでサングラスをかけて角巻わためになりきろう!
Let's all wear the sunglasses and become Tsunomaki Watame!
みんなついてきてますか? 大丈夫ですか?
Is everyone keeping up? Are you all doing okay?
お次は...行きますよ! こちら!!
Next... here we go! This!!
「エア・ギターTシャツ」!
"Air Guitar T-shirt"!
その名の通り、なんとエア・ギターが出来ちゃうTシャツなんですねぇ!
As the name suggests, it's a T-shirt that lets you play air guitar!
わためも実はちょっとエア・ギターを練習中!
Watame is actually practicing air guitar a bit too!
曲に合わせて一緒にかき鳴らそう〜!
Let's strum along to the music together!
これで終わりじゃありません!! 次のグッズはこちら!!
That's not all!! The next item is this!!
「もこもこキャップ」! かわいい〜
"Fluffy Cap"! So cute~
羊をイメージして作ったカジュアルなキャップです!
A casual cap designed with a sheep motif!
ライブだけでなく普段でも使えるおしゃれなアイテム!
A stylish item you can use not just at lives, but every day!
ラストスパート行きますよ〜! お次はこちら〜!
Going into the home stretch! Next is this!
「ラバーコースター」!
"Rubber Coaster"!
ギターピックの形になっているので、これでギターを弾くも良し、飾るも良し、飲み物の下に敷くも良し!
It's shaped like a guitar pick, so you can play guitar with it, display it, or use it under your drink!
そして...最後のグッズはこれだ〜!!
And... the final item is this!!
「セトリキーホルダー」! 今日のライブのセットリストがキーホルダーになります!
"Setlist Keychain"! Today's live setlist becomes a keychain!
ライブであんな曲やこんな曲やってたな〜って思い出してくれたら嬉しいです!
I'd be happy if it reminds you of all the songs we performed today!
詳しくは公演サイトと販売サイトチェックしてみてね〜!
Check out the concert and sales sites for details!
以上!! 角巻わためより2ndライブグッズ紹介をお送りしました〜!
That's all!! This has been a 2nd live merchandise intro from Tsunomaki Watame!
わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to stage effects, please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援 OK です
Vocal cheering is permitted.
各楽曲の演出に合わせてペンライトのカラーを切り替えて、
会場演出のお手伝いをお願いします。
Please help with the venue's atmosphere by switching
penlight colors to match each song's performance.
角巻わため 2nd Live 応援セット ¥14,600
Tsunomaki Watame 2nd Live Support Set - ¥14,600
Item Lineup ①
Item Lineup ②
セトリキーホルダー ¥2,400 / ラバーコースター ¥900
Setlist Keychain ¥2,400 / Rubber Coaster ¥900
わため愛してる
Watame, I love you
Attention
撮影・録音禁止
No Photography or Recording
Goods Lineup
本日は角巻わためセカンドライブ
Today, at Tsunomaki Watame's 2nd Live,
「わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER」に
"Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER,"
ご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
thank you very much for coming.
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意並びにご案内申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the performance, we have some precautions and information for the audience.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機器の使用は...
The use of photography, audio, or video recording equipment during the performance is...
また、固くお断りいたします。
We also strictly prohibit such actions.
館内は禁煙となっております。
The venue is non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮くださいますようお願い申し上げます。
Please refrain from smoking inside.
万が一体調に異変を感じる場合は、
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell,
無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
please do not overdo it and inform a staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、肩車、ステージ上に物を投げ込む、
Moshing, diving, shoulder rides, throwing objects on stage,
ステージ上に上がる、故意に通路を塞ぐ、前に押し寄せる、
getting on stage, blocking aisles, or pushing forward,
周りのお客様のご迷惑となるような不自然なコール、叫声、公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らす等の行為、
disturbing shouts, loud noises, or any behavior that
nuisances others or interferes with the show,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、
violently waving your hands side-to-side
at unnatural timings,
腕を振り回す、上半身を反らすなどの過激な応援行為、過度なジャンプ行為等、他のお客様のご迷惑になる、公演を妨げる危険行為は一切禁止です。
extreme cheering like swinging arms or bending backwards,
excessive jumping, and other dangerous acts are prohibited.
係員の指示及び注意に従わずに生じた事故や機材破損、トラブルについて、主催者、出演者、関係各所は一切の責任を負いかねます。
Organizers and performers are not responsible for any
accidents or damage caused by ignoring instructions.
また、前記指示、注意を無視して生じた機材破損やトラブル等における損害補償は、加害者の責任となりますことあらかじめご了承ください。
Please note that compensation for damage resulting from
ignoring warnings will be the responsibility of the perpetrator.
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席のお客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Please be aware that cameras for recording and streaming
may capture images of the audience.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
These images and videos may be used for promotional
purposes. Thank you for your understanding.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now, please wait a moment until the performance begins.
どどどどどーーー！
Dododododo---!
俺の名前を言ってみろー！
Say my name!
わためー！
Watame!
いぇーい！
Yay!
今日は最高に楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's have the best time today!
もうちょっと待っててね！
Please wait just a bit more!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
WATAME TSUNOMAKI presents
Are you ready for WNF!?
わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
WOWOH!
わためぇ Night Fever!!
Watame Night Fever!!
Hey! Tokyo Garden Theater!!
みんなもっと声出せるよなー！
Everyone, you can shout louder, right?!
みんなの声聞かせて！
Let me hear your voices!
WOWOH!
まだまだー！
More, more!
ありがとう！もっと踊ってー！
Thank you! Dance more!
見栄っ張りで寂しんぼ
Vain and lonely
意外と甘えん坊
Surprisingly a spoiled child
意外とお慌てん坊
Surprisingly a scatterbrain
意外と照れ屋
Surprisingly shy
丸い羊雲
Round sheep cloud
飛び出した好奇心
Popped out curiosity
負けず嫌いな
Hates to lose
溜まるフラストレーション
Accumulating frustration
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢見心地
Fluffy floating dreamy feeling
ひとつひとつ数えておやすみなさい
Count them one by one, good night
密かに芽生えたこの気持ち
This feeling that secretly sprouted
まっすぐ見つめないで
Don't look straight at me
なんだっけ？
What was it?
嘘つきじゃなきゃ生きてけないのじゃなくて
It's not that I can't live without being a liar
てじゃなくてじゃらけじゃなくて
It's not, it's not, it's not...
本当の本当は隠したいんじゃないの
The truth is, I don't want to hide it
そうじゃないのにな
Even though that's not it
Wow oh...
曖昧じゃなくてこの気持ちは間違いじゃない
It's not vague, this feeling is not a mistake
指切りげんまん
Pinky swear
かなり意固地で
Quite stubborn
優柔不断でも
Even if indecisive
絶対に毎日
Definitely every day
会いに来てくれるよな！
You'll come to see me, right?!
笑い臆病で
Laughing cowardly
強がりな気持ち
A feeling of pretending to be strong
全然変わらずに
Without changing at all
グッバイ、君ばっか
Goodbye, only you
当たり前のよう
Like it's natural
結局拙者
In the end, I—
君がどっかりしちゃう
—am sitting heavily on you.
ホントのホントにしょんぼりしちゃうわ
I'll be really, really downcast.
会いたくなっちゃうわ
I'll want to see you.
公開脱走
A public escape.
この心も雪崩しちゃえ
Let this heart avalanche too.
この指とまれ！
Put your finger here!
弱いところ気づかれたり
Having my weak spots noticed,
寂しさごと包まれたり
Being wrapped up along with my loneliness,
いつまでも笑い合ったり
Laughing together forever,
たまにはちょっと喧嘩をしたり
Sometimes having a little fight...
ずっとずっとそばにいてほしい
I want you to stay by my side forever and ever.
約束だぞ！
It's a promise!
言っちゃった もしかしたら運命かも
I said it; maybe it's fate.
赤い糸 ピンと張っちゃうかも
The red thread might be pulled tight.
ホントのホントは バレてるのかも
The absolute truth might have been found out.
目合わせられないかも
I might not be able to meet your eyes.
あいまいなんて言わせない
I won't let you call it vague.
ほら私を見てて
Look, look at me.
指切りだ！
Pinky promise!
つれづれ 髪を解くの 枕の上
Idly undoing my hair on the pillow.
つれづれ 解れた表紙の上
Idly on the frayed cover.
ドドドド ドライブして
Do-do-do-do driving.
ギギギギ ギア入れて
Ge-ge-ge-gear in.
パパパパ 片付けて
Pa-pa-pa-pa tidying up.
さあ 踊りましょう
Now, let's dance.
踊らせて もっと もっと
Make me dance more, more.
全力は ドッと ドッと
Full power is surging.
今すぐに ダイブ 飛び込んでけ
Right now, dive in!
ダダダダ ダンスまだ 踊っちゃって
Da-da-da-da dancing still.
ダダダダ ダンス終わんなくたって
Da-da-da-da even if the dance doesn't end.
てててて 手繋いで 踊っちゃって
Te-te-te-te holding hands and dancing.
じゃんじゃんじゃん テンポ乗っちゃって
Jan-jan-jan getting on the tempo.
けけけけ 蹴っ飛ばしちゃって
Ke-ke-ke-ke kicking it away.
捕まった この世界 感じちゃって
Caught in this world, feel it.
たまんないのさ ステップ
I can't get enough of this step.
つれづれ ワンビートの上
Idly on one beat.
それぞれ 揺らしてく この場で
Each swaying in this place.
スススス スライドして
Sl-sl-sl-slide.
ツツツツ 繋いで
Co-co-co-connect.
ココココ こんばんは
Go-go-go-good evening.
さあ 踊りましょう
Now, let's dance.
踊らせて もっと もっと
Make me dance more, more.
かみさまは ゴッと ゴッと
God is—surging.
楽しみたいなら フロアへ チョコ
If you want to have fun, to the floor, choco!
ダダダダ ダンスまだ 踊っちゃって
Da-da-da-da dancing still.
すべて、全て、気にしないで
Don't care about anything at all
踊っちゃって
Just dance
ララララ 楽しく笑っちゃって
La-la-la-la, laugh and have fun
テテテテ テンザッツハッピーで
Te-te-te-te, That's Happy
舞って、舞って
Dance, dance
どうせ
Anyway
テンアゲになっちゃって
Get hyped up
つまり最高
In other words, the best
Step, Oh-Oh
踊ってる
I'm dancing
揺いでる
I'm swaying
ミラーボールが回ってる
The mirror ball is spinning
踊ってる
I'm dancing
踊ってよ
Keep dancing
終わりが来るまでずっと
Until the very end
踊り明かそう
Let's dance the night away
誰よりも、マッザ、マッザ
More than anyone, Mudder, Mudder
点々は、ドッザ、ドッザ
Dots are, Dodda, Dodda
今すぐに大気飛び越えて
Leap across the atmosphere right now
ドドドド ダンシング
Do-do-do-do Dancing
さらば、だって
Because, goodbye
ママママ マシン走行だって
Ma-ma-ma-ma Machine-like running
ステップ捨てて見つめ合って
Discard the steps and look at each other
踊っちゃって
Just dance
ジャジャジャジャ じゃんけんで勝っちゃって
Ja-ja-ja-ja, win at rock-paper-scissors
ケケケケ けっぱずんじゃって
Ke-ke-ke-ke, kick it off
舞って、舞って
Dance, dance
可能性
Possibility
テンアゲになっちゃって
Get hyped up
つまり最高
In other words, the best
Step, Oh-Oh
踊ってよ
Keep dancing
何がある？ それまでのカラクリ
What was there? The mechanism until then
しょうがないけど 歩み進める
It can't be helped, but I'll step forward
振り返ることもできるけど
I can also look back, but
それは、ほどほどでもいいよね
that should be kept in moderation, right?
わかるなんて言葉はいつも
The word "understand" is always
綺麗事だけど信じていた
just a lip service, but I believed in it
なんとかなれ、なんにでもなれ
Let it be something, let it become anything
もうさ、強い気持ちで
Now, with a strong feeling
ヒカレ、いつだって その瞳
Shine, always that gaze
輝きを失うまでは
Until it loses its sparkle
ヒカレ、そのままで構わない
Shine, it's fine just as you are
いずれ 輝ける日が来るさ
One day, the time to sparkle will come
きっと
Surely
しくじる時もたまにある
Sometimes things go wrong
燃え尽きることではなくて
It's not about burning out
何がある？ 揺れ動く感情
What is there? These moving emotions
答えめいたものはないけど
There's nothing like an answer, but
君が触れたその感触は
That sensation you touched
君だけにしかわからないよ
Only you can understand it
悔しいことバネにできない
I can't turn frustrations into motivation
そんな時もあるよね
There are times like that, right?
ヒラケ、心の中の扉
Open, the door in your heart
少しずつ トンネル抜けて
Little by little, exiting the tunnel
ヒラケ、時間はかかるけれど
Open, it takes time, but
いずれ 開かれる日が来るさ
One day, the time to open will come
きっと
Surely
いつか サイコー
Someday the best
…を手に入れて
…into my hands,
いつか聞いた
One day I heard
あのフレーズを
that phrase.
いつか思い描いた
The star I once
星を
imagined,
いつか大声で叫んでみる
I'll try shouting it out loud one day.
きっと…
Surely…
角巻わためー！
Tsunomaki Watame!
2ndライブ わためぇ Night Fever!!
Thank you all for coming to my 2nd Live,
in TOKYO GARDEN THEATERに来てくれてありがとう！
Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER!
緊張するわー
I'm so nervous.
でも、みんなの声聞こえるよ
But I can hear all of your voices!
すごい！
Amazing!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、震え上がってるよ、
Wow, the Garden Theater is shaking!
ガーデンシアターが。本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
1stからのね、約2年ぶりということで
It's been about two years since my 1st Live.
1stも来た人いる？
Is there anyone here who came to the 1st one?
ああ、結構いる！
Oh, quite a lot!
今日が初めての人？
Anyone here for the first time today?
いやー、嬉しいね。いっぱい来てくれてありがとうございます。
Wow, I'm so happy. Thank you so much for coming.
ね、みんな、新しいアルバムは聞いてくれた？
Hey everyone, did you listen to my new album?
すごい、みんな聞いてくれてる！ありがとうございます！
Amazing, everyone listened to it! Thank you so much!
いや、楽しいね。
This is so much fun.
楽しいね！
It's fun!
今回は、ドドドバンドによる生演奏でのライブとなっております！
This live features a live performance by the DODODO BAND!
みんな、素敵なバンドメンバーなんで、紹介してもいいですか？
They're all wonderful band members. May I introduce them?
ありがとう。ちょっとやってみたかったんだよ、これ。
Thank you. I've always wanted to do this.
嬉しいよ。じゃあ、やらせていただきます。
I'm so happy. Well then, here we go.
On Bass, あさちゃんこと、朝倉高昭！
On Bass, Asakura Takaaki, also known as Asachan!
あさちゃーん！
Asachan!
すごい、あさちゃーん！
Amazing, Asachan!
すごいね、みんな優しいね。ありがとうございます。
Wow, everyone's so kind. Thank you.
まだまだいるからね。
There are still more.
On Drums, たっくんこと、西澤琢実！
On Drums, Nishizawa Takumi, also known as Takkun!
たっくーん！
Takkun!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして、On Keyboard, たつんだ、ジョー！
And on Keyboard... stand up, Joe!
弾くんだ、ジョー！
Play it, Joe!
キーボード弾けー！
Play that keyboard!
とってもパリピなジョーです。
That's Joe, he's quite the party person.
盛り上がってるよ。ありがとう。
Things are heating up. Thank you.
そして、On Guitar & バンドマスターを務めていただいております、おけはんこと、井手景介！
And on Guitar, our band master, Ide Keisuke, also known as Okehan!
おけはーん！
Okehan!
ええー、いいな、いいな。そして、
Wow, that's great. And...
On Vocal!
角巻わため！
Tsunomaki Watame!
嬉しい、羊もいるな。
I'm happy, there are sheep too.
羊がいるな。声でかい羊がいるな。
I see sheep. There's a loud sheep.
こちらの、ドドドバンドと一緒に今日は盛り上げていきたいと思います！
I want to rock out today with the DODODO BAND!
でもさ、みんなもメンバーじゃない？ね？
But you know, you're all members too, right?
ちょっとコール＆レスポンスやっていい？
Can I do a little call and response?
じゃあまず、いるかな？女の子ー、イエーイ！
First off, are you there? Girls, yeah!
あ、聞こえる。女の子ー！
Ah, I hear you. Girls!
女の子だー！
There are girls!
すごい！すごい！ありがとう！嬉しい！
Amazing! Amazing! Thank you! I'm so happy!
しきぴ、ありがとう！
Shikipi, thank you!
そして、男のコ〜！
And, boys!
うお、すごい！すげえぜ！声デカ！
Whoa, amazing! Incredible! So loud!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
男のコも、しきぴ！
Boys too, Shikipi!
ありがとう！じゃあ、全員聞かせてくれ！イエーイ！
Thank you! Now, everyone, let me hear you! Yeah!
すごいな〜！気持ちいい！
Amazing! This feels great!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
もちろん、配信組のみんなの番もあるよ！
Of course, it's the streaming group's turn too!
配信組のみんな〜！
Everyone in the streaming group!
イエーイ！コメント見えてますよ〜！
Yeah! I can see your comments!
「景色いいなあ」って言ってる人いるわ。
Someone's saying the view is beautiful.
ね、ありがとう！
Right? Thank you!
え、ちょっとやりたいことまだある。ペンライトウェーブ！
Wait, there's something else I want to do. Penlight wave!
ペンライト、持ってますか？
Do you have your penlights?
いやみんな持ってるな。ありがとうございます。
Man, everyone has them. Thank you very much.
ファーストの時にやったウェーブやっていいですか？
Can I do the wave we did at the first live?
こっちから行きますよ。
Starting from this side.
いくよ。
Here we go.
イエーイ！
Yeah!
こっちも！
This side too!
ついてこれてる？
Are you keeping up?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
ついてこれてない？大丈夫かな？
Not keeping up? Is everyone okay?
いや楽しいね！
Man, this is fun!
最高だ！
This is the best!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
今日はね、なんと韓国でもライブビューイングをしておりまして。
Today, believe it or not, we're having a live viewing in Korea.
韓国のみんな、アンニョンハセヨ〜！
Everyone in Korea, annyeonghaseyo!
カムサハムニダ！
Kamsahamnida!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今日はね、ライブの感想をハッシュタグ #わためセカンドライブ でたくさんポストしてください！
Today, please post lots of live impressions using the hashtag #WatameSecondLive!
今日はね、みんなと一緒に作り上げるライブだと思っているので...
Today, I think of this as a live we create together with everyone...
ペンライト振ったり、タオルを回したり、エアギターを弾いたり...
Waving penlights, twirling towels, playing air guitar...
...したいと思っております！
...that's what I want to do!
できますか？
Can you do it?
できそうだね。頼むよ。
Looks like you can. I'm counting on you.
そして、ステージに表示されるコール、言葉、歌詞、一緒に歌ってください！
And the calls, words, and lyrics displayed on stage, please sing along!
お願いします！
Please!
なんとここで悲報です。
And now, I have some sad news.
YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方はここまでとなります。
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is where it ends.
みんな一緒に最後までいたいよね？
Everyone wants to stay together until the end, right?
一緒に盛り上がりたいよね？
You want to get hyped together, right?
概要欄から配信サイトへチケットを買っていただいて...
Please buy a ticket to the streaming site from the description...
最後まで一緒にいようよ！
...and let's stay together until the end!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
「買ってね」って。ありがとうございます。
Someone said "Buy it". Thank you very much.
今回はね、いっぱいちょっと曲用意してきたから...
This time, I've prepared quite a lot of songs...
早速次の曲に行きたいと思います！
...so I'd like to move on to the next song right away!
次の曲もニューアルバムから。
The next song is also from the new album.
バンドのみんな、演奏よろしく！
Band, let's play!
無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has concluded.
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free portion has ended.
Thank you for watching!